Guide to the Carl B. Hess Papers MC.229
New York University Archives
Carl B. Hess Papers
1925-2011
New York University Archives
Hess, Carl B., 1912-2011
Hess, Ludmilla
MC.229
25.50 Linear Feet in 47 manuscript boxes, 1 small flat box, 2 oversize flat boxes, and 2 card boxes.
Carl B. Hess (1912-2011) graduated from Dartmouth College in 1934 and was the founder and Chairman Emeritus of AEA Investors, working primarily with private equities. This collection contains research and staff interview transcripts related to the 1993 AEA Investors corporate history book Profit with Honor, written by Hess' brother John D. Hess. Business and personal correspondence in this collection dates from the 1920s to 2010s, and includes appointment books from the 1940s to 2011, as well as alphabetical office Rolodex cards. Files and interview transcripts related to the 2005 book Dilworth Here, a tribute to Hess' friend J. Richardson Dilworth, are in this collection. Personal files include Hess' artwork in the form of drawings, ink sketches, and cartoons, as well as documentation from experiences in high school and Dartmouth College the 1920s and 1930s, including class papers, ephemera, and publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to Box 49 is restricted until 2036. The remaining materials in the collection are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Material was donated by Ludmila Hess, 2011.
Appraisal
In 2021 four manuscript boxes of material belonging in other collections were reviewed by the University Archivist, removed, and either shredded or added to the appropriate collection.
Material related to existing company records, personal financial information, and some personal correspondence were removed from the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in three series:
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Personal
Series III. Professional
The files within the series are arranged chronologically, with materials grouped by subject and arranged chronologically within.
Biographical Note
Carl B. Hess (1912-2011) graduated from Dartmouth College in 1934. He became the director of development at Cresap, McCormick, and Paget, a management consultant firm, until he moved on to the American Securities Corporation. In 1968 he co-founded the private investment firm, AEA Investors. Hess remained as chairman and president AEA until 1989. From 1989 until his retirement in 2000 he served as chairman of AEA's executive committee.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the personal and business files accumulated by Carl B. Hess from the 1920s to 2011. The collection includes his personal and business correspondence dating from the 1920s to the 2010s, and his datebooks and contact Rolodex cards dating from the 1950s to the 2010s. Material specifically documenting Hess's work in the private equity sector includes a small amount of files on the founding of AEA Investors, as well as his brother John D. Hess' work files and executive interview transcripts for the AEA corporate history book, Profit with Honor. Files on some of his earlier positions at other companies in the 1950s and 1960s are also in this collection. Hess' artwork was created during the 1920s and 1930s for his high school's publications and event posters, and later for Dartmouth College publications and sports event programs. Dartmouth College ephemera from the early 1930s and work files and interview transcripts related to the book Dilworth Here are also in this collection.
Corporations, American; Investments.; Political cartoons.; Drawings, pen and ink.; Interviews.; Hess, Ludmilla; Hess, John D. (John David), 1918-2004; Dartmouth College; Dilworth, J. Richardson (Joseph Richardson), 1916-1997
- Series I. Correspondence, 1927-2009; 6.67 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes.
  Arrangement
  This series has been arranged beginning with early personal letters, followed by files arranged alphabetically by last name, and ending with chronologically organized correspondence files.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to Box 49 is restricted until 2036.
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes correspondence with personal and professional contacts dating from the 1920s to 2010. Letters from Hess' family, including his mother, stepfather, and brother John, as well as from various friends, document Hess' experience while he attended Dartmouth College from 1931-1934. Additional letters with family members date from the 1940s to the 1960s. Correspondence files organized alphabetically by last name are mostly business associates who were also considered friends, including J. Richardson Dilworth, Maurice Greenberg, George Love, and Vincent Mai. The chronologically arranged files include both business and personal letters, dating from 1970 to 2008. Some correspondence files also contain press clippings, speeches, and event programs.
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- From Mother, Stepfather, Brother John, 1927-1934 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- General, 1928-1979, undated (Box 1, Folder 6-7, Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- From Hess to Family While Attending Dartmouth College, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- Selz, Maggie, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- Spiegel, Marj, 1933-1935, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- Warburg, Andrea, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- From Family and Friends Re: Hess Trip to Montana, Idaho, Colorado, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- From John Hess and Wife Jane, 1941-1968, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4-6, Box 4)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- Freund, Dick, 1942-1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- From Mother, Stepfather, 1947-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4-7)
  - Early Personal Correspondence -- Birthday Notes to Hess, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Akers, John RESTRICTED, 1986-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Adams, John B., 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AEA -- "Family" Letters, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - AEA -- GAB / UAL Congratulatory Letters, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Al-Sudairy, Ziad RESTRICTED, 1991-1996 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Burke, James E., 1980s-2000s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Caldwell, Philip RESTRICTED, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Howard L., 1982-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Danforth, Douglas, 1988, 1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dilworth Family, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1980-1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Doede, John, 1980-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dudley, James C., 1985-1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Flom, Joseph H., 1996-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Freedman, James O., 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Golden, William, 1961-1962, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, George J., 1983-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - Greenberg, Maurice R. RESTRICTED, 1989-2005 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Ho, Chin, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Howell, David RESTRICTED, 2007-2009 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Ireland, R.L., III, 1986-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jamison, J. Kenneth, 1982-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Colin, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Reginald, 1989-2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1984-2009 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lazarus, Ralph RESTRICTED, 1976-1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Littlefield, Edmund W. RESTRICTED, 1986-2001 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Love, George, 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Love, Howard M., 1989-2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - McLaughlin, David T. (Dartmouth), 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Monahan, Francois, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Morlion, Felix, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Morton, Alastair, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mueller, Carl M., 1984-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "N" Correspondence, 1968-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "O" Correspondence, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "P" Correspondence, 1973-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "R" Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "S" Correspondence, 1971-1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Shapiro, Irving S., 1980-2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Singh, D.J., 1956, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Stanley, Justin A., 1958-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Stillman, Robert, 1967, 1984-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "T" Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Temple, Robert W., 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tennison, Harry L., 1979, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Torno, Noah, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-Nine Club (Paul Chase), 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "W" Correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - S.G. Warburg and Company-Related, 1965-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7-10, Box 8, Folder 1-6, Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Wharton, John, 1959-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Whitehead, John C., 1985-2009 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wingate, Paul D., 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Weill, Harold, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Wyatt, Harry N., 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5-6, Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5-6, Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7, Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8, Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 5-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Series II. Personal, 1925-2011; 8 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes, 1 small flat box, and 2 oversize flat boxes.
  This series contains materials related to Hess' personal life, artwork, high school and college experiences, and a later book project from the 2000s. Early art study files include pencil and ink sketches, cartoons, and color pencil drawings, along with mail order lesson books and exercises from W.L. Evans. The cartoon artworks in this series were often used in both high school and later college publications, and often humorously address school-specific topics. Materials related to the University of Chicago High School date from the late 1920s and include class papers, ephemera, and school publications with Hess' cartoons. Poster-size and smaller painted artwork images for the high school yearbook The Correlator are also in this series. This series also includes Hess' Dartmouth College ephemera, class papers and exams, his The Dartmouth editor's notebook, and sports programs and school publications containing his cartoons. The series also contains a small number of files on the temperance movement that had been accumulated by Hess, including drafts of articles written and various organizational brochures. Files in this series relate to the 2005 book commissioned by Hess to honor J. Richardson Dilworth, Dilworth Here, and include communications with the author, copies of the book, responses from readers, and interview transcripts with Dilworth friends, dating from the early 2000s.
  - Culver School of Woodcraft -- Brochures, Reports, Certificates, and Publication Containing Hess Cartoons, 1925-1930 (Box 15, Folder 4, Box 50, Folder 6)
  - W.L. Evans School of Cartooning Lesson Books and Evaluated Exercise Sketches, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Drawings, Colored Sketches, and Cartoons, 1925-1930 (Box 15, Folder 6-12, Box 16, Folder 1-3, Box 51, Folder 1, Box 50, Folder 5, 7-13, 15, Box 52)
  - Kenwood Graduation Program, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago High School -- Correspondence, Ephemera, Class Papers, School Publications with Hess Artwork; Yearbook Graphic Boards with Drawings, 1927-1930 (Box 16, Folder 5-11, Box 50, Folder 1-4, Box 51, Folder 2-3, Box 52, Folder 4-6)
  - Printing Blocks Containing Hess Photographic Portrait, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth College -- Exams, Papers, Ephemera, 1930-1934 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Dartmouth College -- Drawings, Sketches for Sports Events, 1931, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Dartmouth College -- Jack-o-Lantern Publications with Hess Artwork, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth College -- Football Programs with Hess Artwork, 1931, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth College -- The Dartmouth Article Scrapbook and Editorial Notebook; Issues of Newspaper, 1932-1933 (Box 17, Folder 6-7, Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth College -- School-Related Communications, 1932-1941 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Dartmouth College -- Hess' The Dartmouth City Editor Correspondence, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Dartmouth College -- The Junto, and Casque and Gauntlet -- Correspondence, Student Bob Michelet Memorial Material, 1933-1941 (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
  - Dartmouth College -- School-related Letters, Invitations, Reports, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Prohibition and Temperance -- Related Articles, Correspondence, and Research, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Loose Notes and Writings -- For Classes, Articles, 1931-1936 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hess and Wife Julia Honeymoon to Guatemala and Mexico -- Receipts, Notes, Ephemera, May 1941 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Dilworth Here -- Notes, Letters, Chapter Drafts, 1996-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2-5)
  - Dilworth Here -- Interviews, Invoices, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 6-7, Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Dilworth Here -- Reader Responses, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5-8)
  - Dilworth Here -- Book, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hess 95th Birthday Party -- Invitation List, Schedule, Notes, Letters, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hess Personal Stationary, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Obituary Notes, circa 2011 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Series III. Professional, 1942-2011; 12 Linear Feet in 27 manuscript boxes and 2 card boxes.
  Files in this series document Hess's career in the private equity business sector. This series includes Hess' datebooks from the early 1950s to 2011 and Rolodex cards with personal and business contacts. Files related to some of his early positions within various corporations include material from American Securities Corporation (ASC) and Cresap, McCormick and Page dating from the 1950s and 1960s. Hess was also the founding chairman and a leader of AEA Investors for many years beginning in the late 1960s. Files related to the company include notes, press clippings, memos, and shareholder meeting speeches. The majority of the AEA material relates to the 1993 corporate history book Profit with Honor, written by Hess' brother John D. Hess. Book files include notes, drafts, copies of the book, and alphabetized staff interview transcripts conducted in the 1980s. Hess' travel files in this series date from 1969 to 1991, and often contain letters, itineraries, and supporting information for business and personal trips.
  - Business-related Notes and Memos, 1940s (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Daily Diary, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Column Magazine Issue -- Carl and John Hess Magazine, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cresap, McCormick and Page -- Notes, Memos, Survey Report, 1949-1953 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Appointment Books, 1951-1960 (Box 22, Folder 4-5, Box 23, Folder 1-4, Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - Appointment Books, 1961-1970 (Box 24, Folder 4-5, Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  - Appointment Books, 1971-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4, Box 26, Folder 1-4, Box 27)
  - Appointment Books, 1980-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1-4, Box 29, Box 30)
  - Appointment Books, 1991-1999 (Box 31, Folder 1-4, Box 32, Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Books, 2000-2011 (Box 33, Folder 2-4, Box 34, Folder 1-4, Box 35, Folder 1-5)
  - Memo -- Discussion in Home of J.S. Seidman with Hess and Others, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Rolodex Contact Cards (A-Z), circa 1958-2011 (Box 36, Box 37)
  - American Securities Corporation -- Survey Template, Memos, Press Releases, 1952-1958 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
  - National Industrial Conference Board Inc. -- Economics for Executives Course Program, Teaching Script, Letters, Schedule, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
  - American European Associates -- Founding Concept Notes, Memos, Proposal, Drafts, Founding Documents Book, 1960-2003 (Box 38, Folder 6-13, Box 39)
  - American European Associates -- Hess Employment Contracts, Agreements RESTRICTED, 1969-1997 (Box 49, Folder 9-16)
  - American European Associates -- Press Clippings, Press Releases, Opening Announcement Cards, 1968-1989 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
  - American European Associates -- First Board of Directors Letter, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Memos, Notes, Vouchers, Position Description, 1970-1985 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - American European Associates -- Staff Meeting Notes, 1973-1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - American European Associates -- Board of Directors Hess Speech, Letters, 1978-2011 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Hess List of Appointments in New York City, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Annual Shareholders Meeting Speech Scripts, Memos, Lists, 1984-1993 (Box 40, Folder 3-7)
  - American European Associates -- List of 1976-1986 Hess Directorships, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - American European Associates -- Hess Retirement Letter, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - American European Associates -- Investor's Informational Booklet, circa 1998 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - American European Associates -- Hess Chairman Emeritus Stationary, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor -- John Hess Interview Notes RESTRICTED, 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 17-18)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Baird, Chip, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Blanchard, Dick, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Bradshaw, Thornton "Brad", 1986 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Canning, John, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Clark Jr., Howard L., 1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Clegg, Steve, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Crisp, Peter, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Crown, Lester, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Dayton, Bruce, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Dilworth, Dick, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Doede, John, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Dudley, Jim, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Eaton, Fred, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Finch, John, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Garnett, Keith, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Garvin, Cliff, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Greenberg, George, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Harper, John, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Hatfield, Bob, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Haynes, Bill, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Hess Carl, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Hewitt, Bill, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Ireland, Tim, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Jamieson, Ken, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Jones, Reg, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Key, Steve, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Lazarus, Ralph, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Leitner, Paul, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Littlefield, Edward, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Love, George, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Mai, Vincent, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Markley, Lee, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Mueller, Carl, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Opel, John, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Patterson, Pat, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Pilliod, Chuck, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Roehm, McDonnell "Don", 1991 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Russell, George, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Salice, Tom, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Seligman, Geoffrey, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Serfass, William, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Shapiro, Irving, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Skelsey, Henry, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Stanton, Frank, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Stevens, Jim, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Stillman, Bob, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 9-11)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Stinson, George, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Taylor, Bud, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Vogelstein, John, circa 1985-1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Warren, Louis, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Weymouth, George, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 3)